要維持和諧真惱人
Harmony is at wit's end
但你能否感到我的心在你身邊？
But can you feel my heart against yours?
被群群陌生的臉龐包圍
Surrounded by unfamiliar faces
只有你的能給我光源
only yours can bring me hope
大家都說，心處於家園
They say that home is where the heart is
但我的心，已裂成兩半
but my heart is split in two
你知我，有如從頭到尾
You know me right from top to bottom
你知我如，我知己
you know me for who I am
你要微笑，微笑，微笑
You gotta smile smile smile
壞事會過去
And it'll be okay
就等一會
You just wait
在這友誼的旅途
And on the road to friendship
傷口會漸漸痊癒
the wounds we had will heal
我們走了很遠
We've come a long way
遠離以往的破裂
from the brokenness we were
他們取的綽號
And the names they say
他們玩的戲弄
And the games they play
非禮勿言
Sticks and stones
但，沒關係
But it's okay
我們再次上路
We're on our way
通往人生的道路
on the road to life again
一個偉大冒險
A great adventure's
就在那之後
just beyond the place
那頭，什麼，都新鮮
where everything is new
噢，好多可能性
Oh, the possibilities
我們在腦中想像著
brought by our imagination
我想，我們可以洗心革面
I think we can work to feel better
因為我們仍活在夢中
Because we're living off a dream of ours
一個充滿魔法的夢境
a dream that's filled with magic
一個充滿希望的未來
A future filled with hope again
我們真是脆弱
We are so fragile
我們的光，熄滅
The lights we've known go dim
腳步逐漸變慢
Our trot becomes a pace
人生也逐漸重來
As our lives transform anew
你要微笑，微笑，微笑
You gotta smile smile smile
壞事會過去
And it'll be okay
但，沒關係
But it's okay
我們再次上路
We're on our way
通往人生的道路
on the road to life again
一個偉大冒險
A great adventure's
就在那之後
just beyond the place
那頭，什麼，都新鮮
where everything is new
我這一生
All my life
永遠只知道，怎麼落荒而逃
all I've known is running away
現在我知道
Now I know
我能挺著身
that I can stand
為了我和我朋友
for myself and for my friends
噢...
Oh...
我能否被原諒？
Can I be forgiven
在那頭
In the place
那頭什麼都新鮮...
where everything is new?